A Guide to the Nancy Florence Architectural Collection, 1954-2014
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Major Projects - Edgewater
  - Reference Files
    - Composition book - Legend Book III Edgewater 93, 94 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Edgewater 1992 + 1994 to 2/6/95 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Edgewater Task Journal #2 - to December 92 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - EW Tasks 12/92 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Key Decisions (Wall, Roof, Loft) (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Casing Details (Door, Window) (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Edgewater Details Box 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - EW References, Consultants (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - USGs Maps + Local (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Site Visit Agendas (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Joints in Header Trim-Plan (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Square Footage (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Structural XS Details #6-12 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Directory E.W. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Blue Binder: Shapiro Edgewater Detail Set (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Construction Record History (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - EW Selected Files (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Edgewater Schedules (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Design Record Copies-Edgewater (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Structural-Edgewater Clips 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - TDC 1991-01 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Wall Finishes (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Odds & Ends (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Transmittals-Edgewater 8/92 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Strict Decisions Edgewater (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Records of Decisions-Edgewater (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Edgewater House Notes (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Edgewater House-Site Fold Reports (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Structural Transmittals-Edgewater House (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Transmitted Details and Decisions-Edgewater House (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Edgewater Transmittals 1994-11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Edgewater House: CD Scheduling (1992) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Edgewater House: Roofing (1992) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Edgewater House: Ventilation (1992) #1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Edgewater House: Ventilation (1992) #2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Edgewater Site Revisits (1992-11-09) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Edgewater Residence: Studio Kitchen (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Edgewater Site Plan 4/91 (Box 38)
  - Sketches
    - Loose Drawings and Sketches (Part 1) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Loose Drawings and Sketches (Part 2) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Loose Drawings and Sketches (Part 3) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Loose Drawings and Sketches (Part 4) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Edgewater Site Plans (undeveloped) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Marc LeBlanc Sketches (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Sketch File Edgewater (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Stair to Loft (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Detailed Plans-Shelving (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bench/Veranda Design (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Sketch Pile (n.d.) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Sketch File (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Steel Sketching-Preliminary (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Edgewater House: Details in Progress (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Edgewater Building Compound Plan (Box 39)
    - Remiker Arbor & Trellises (Box 40)
    - Edgewater Residence Revisions (Box 41)
    - Structural Edgewater w/ Truss Study (Last Sheet) (Box 42)
    - House Set (Box 43)
    - Edgewater Residence: Site Plan 10/92 (Box 44)
    - Edgewater Residence: Site Plan 4/93 (Box 45)
    - Edgewater Residence: Site Plan 12/92 (Box 46)
    - Edgewater Residence: Progress 8/92 (Box 47)
    - Edgewater Residence: Progress 1/94 (Box 48)
    - Edgewater Residence: HAC Prelim (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Freehand Sketches and Site Plans (Map-case 22, Folder 11)
    - Design Decisions & History (Map-case 22, Folder 12)
  - Specifications
    - Energy (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Insulation 94 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - General Specs (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Hardware EW (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Ansi Electrical Symbols (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - RMS Energy Equipment (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Doors 1993-11 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Edgewater Materials (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Interior Elevations - Edgewater House (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Edgewater Building Compound Plan (Box 49)
    - Interior Elevations (Map-case 22, Folder 13)
    - Edgwater Residence Drawings (Map-case 22, Folder 14)
    - Edgewater Residence Plans (Map-case 22, Folder 15)
  - Photos
    - Sun Valley Magazine (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Edgewater House Photos (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Artifacts (Box 10)
  - Plastic box with wooden trusses models (Box 10, Folder 1)